[
    {
        "answer": "Breach",
        "question": "Unauthorized access or accidental disclosure of confidential information."
    },
    {
        "answer": "Event",
        "question": "Any observable occurrence in a network or system."
    },
    {
        "answer": "Exploit",
        "question": "A particular attack. It is named this way because these attacks exploit system vulnerabilities."
    },
    {
        "answer": "Incident",
        "question": "An actual or suspected security violation that affects the confidentiality, integrity, or availability of critical information."
    },
    {
        "answer": "Intrusion",
        "question": "Unauthorized access to a system or network."
    },
    {
        "answer": "Threat",
        "question": "A circumstance or event that could cause harm to a system or organization, such as a cyber attack or natural disaster."
    },
    {
        "answer": "Vulnerability",
        "question": "Weakness in an information system, system security procedures, internal controls or implementation that could be exploited by a threat source."
    },
    {
        "answer": "Zero-day",
        "question": "A previously unknown system vulnerability with the potential of exploitation without risk of detection or prevention because it does not, in general, fit recognized patterns, signatures or methods."
    },
    {
        "answer": "Adverse Events",
        "question": "Events with a negative consequence, such as system crashes, network packet floods, unauthorized use of system privileges, defacement of a web page or execution of malicious code that destroys data."
    },
    {
        "answer": "**Business Continuity (BC)**",
        "question": "**Actions, processes and tools for ensuring an organization can continue critical operations during a contingency**"
    },
    {
        "answer": "**Business Continuity Plan (BCP)**",
        "question": "**The documentation of a predetermined set of instructions or procedures that describe how an organization's mission/business processes will be sustained during and after a significant disruption.**"
    },
    {
        "answer": "Business Impact Analysis (BIA)",
        "question": "An analysis of an information system's requirements, functions, and interdependencies used to characterize system contingency requirements and priorities in the event of a significant disruption."
    },
    {
        "answer": "**Disaster Recovery (DR)**",
        "question": "In information systems terms, the activities necessary to restore IT and communications services to an organization during and after an outage, disruption or disturbance of any kind or scale."
    },
    {
        "answer": "**Disaster Recovery Plan (DRP)**",
        "question": "The processes, policies and procedures related to preparing for recovery or continuation of an organization's critical business functions, technology infrastructure, systems and applications after the organization experiences a disaster."
    },
    {
        "answer": "Incident Handling",
        "question": "The mitigation of violations of security policies and recommended practices."
    },
    {
        "answer": "**Incident Response (IR)**",
        "question": "The mitigation of violations of security policies and recommended practices."
    },
    {
        "answer": "**Incident Response Plan (IRP)**",
        "question": "The documentation of a predetermined set of instructions or procedures to detect, respond to and limit consequences of a malicious cyberattack against an organization's information systems(s)."
    },
    {
        "answer": "Security Operations Center",
        "question": "A centralized organizational function fulfilled by an information security team that monitors, detects and analyzes events on the network or system to prevent and resolve issues before they result in business disruptions."
    },
    {
        "answer": "Vulnerability",
        "question": "Weakness in an information system, system security procedures, internal controls or implementation that could be exploited or triggered by a threat source."
    }
]